http://www.themercury.com/site/privacy.html

Home
When accessing our Website, The Manhattan Mercury will learn certain information about you during your visit. How we will handle information we learn about you depends upon what you do when visiting our site.If you visit our site to read or download information on our pages, we collect and store only the following information about you:1. The name of the domain from which you access the Internet2. The date and time you access our site3. The Internet address of the website you used to link directly to our site.If you identify yourself by sending us an e-mail containing personal information, then the information collected will be solely used to respond to your message.The information collected is for statistical purposes. The Manhattan Mercury may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, The Manhattan Mercury uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.The Manhattan Mercury will not obtain personally-identifying information about you when you visit our site, unless you choose to provide such information to us, nor will such information be sold or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user at the time of collection. 1. ONLINE TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES AND ADVERTISINGWe and certain service providers operating on our behalf collect information about your activity, or activity on devices associated with you, on our sites and applications using tracking technologies such as cookies, Flash cookies, pixels, tags, software development kits, application program interfaces, and Web beacons. Definitions for some of the tracking technologies listed, as well as information about your choices with respect to them, are available below. This tracking data may be used for many purposes including, for example, to:Provide useful features to simplify your experience when you return to our sites and applications (for example, remembering your shipping information for future purchases);Deliver relevant content and advertising based on your preferences, usage patterns and location;Monitor, evaluate, and optimize the use and operation of our sites and applications; andAnalyze traffic on our sites and on the sites of third parties.We may collect information whether or not you are logged in or registered, and may associate this tracking data with your registration account (if you have one), in which case we will treat it as personal information. Service providers that collect tracking data on our behalf may provide an opportunity for you to choose not to be tracked online.Advertisers and third parties also may collect information about your activity on our sites and applications, on devices associated with you, and on third-party sites and applications using tracking technologies. Tracking data collected by these advertisers and third parties is used to decide which ads you see both on our sites and applications and on third-party sites and applications.You may choose not to receive targeted advertising from many ad networks and partners, data exchanges, and marketing analytics and other digital advertising and marketing service providers. You may also be able to choose to control targeted advertising on other websites and platforms that you visit. In addition, you may also choose to control targeted advertising you receive within applications by using the settings and controls on your devices (for example, by re-setting your mobile device’s advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads). We adhere to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising.2. Online Tracking TechnologiesExamples of online tracking technologies include:Cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website places on the hard drive of your computer when you visit the website. Cookies may involve the transmission of information from us to you and from you directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use cookies to bring together information we collect about you. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being placed on your device, or you can choose to block all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won’t have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient, and some of our services will not function properly.Flash cookies. We may use local shared objects, sometimes known as Flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Our advertisers and third-party service providers also may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and manner in which data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. Learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies. If you disable Flash cookies, you won’t have access to many features that make your guest experience more efficient, and some of our services will not function properly.Web beacons. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of sites. Web beacons may involve the transmission of information directly to us, to another party on our behalf, or to another party in accordance with its privacy policy. We may use web beacons to bring together information we collect about you.3. Do Not TrackWeb browsers can transmit Do Not Track signals that indicate that a user does not wish to have activity tracked. Currently, no universally accepted standard exists for how to interpret such signals, although work to create consensus is ongoing. Accordingly, we adhere to the standards set out in our privacy policy. You can manage your choices regarding targeted advertising as described in Section 1 above and in Your Controls and Choices. Learn about Do Not Track.
Latest News
K-State women's basketball bounces back to upset No. 22 South Dakota State
Police report for Dec. 10, 2020
Riley County approves lease for COVID-19 alternate care site
Manhattan High prepares for finals while K-State adapts recruitment efforts
I WONDER | Who received the most write-ins for the 2020 presidential election?
PLAN YOUR WEEKEND | Ugly sweater parties, basketball, painting and more
Riley County reports COVID-19 positive test rate of 25.5%
Manhattan native appears in Trump skit on Kimmel show
Most Popular
Articles
Images
Videos
Commented
ArticlesWide receiver Wykeen Gill becomes Kansas State football's latest transfer; count up to 12Former MHS teacher, K-State graduate wins $21K on 'Jeopardy'Defensive back Lance Robinson becomes 11th Kansas State player in transfer portalBruce Weber: 'I apologize' to Kansas State fan base after embarrassing loss to Fort Hays StateOUR NEIGHBORS | From Micronesia to Manhattan, hibachi chef serves flavor, entertainmentWhat to make of Kansas State football's plethora of transfersWinless Fort Hays State stuns Kansas State's men's basketball 81-68K-State virus experts carry on research roles in global COVID-19 battleWhen will 2 Kansas State men's basketball newcomers make their debuts?Dennis Kuhlman
Images
Videos
CommentedSorry, there are no recent results for popular commented articles.
Latest e-Edition
The Manhattan Mercury
To view our latest e-Edition click the image on the left.
© Copyright 2020 themercury.com, 318 N 5th Street Manhattan, KS | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
